From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche
Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringing love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has, don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream
Hey Chanel. Hi guys. How are you?
Hopefully you're good. Okay. You like that? Thank you so much Blue Ring. Nice to see you.
Yeah, I mean I did have just have a short kind of members,
members only thing. I'll think I'll do that maybe once a week. You know it's just good to check in
with members and make sure everyone's happy and getting
You know feeling that they're getting getting their value and everything so
Thank you Chanel
Yeah, I want to do some more to get my shirt too. I got the shirt
Another cool T move finds. I live the starry night at the kitty cat
Thank you so much
Yeah
You know, I've been working a lot with the, you know, chat GPT and said, hey, Sponky, how are you? Happy Sunday, everybody. Thank you. Thank you guys.
DJ Electra made a couple of the intros. I made a couple of the intros with AI and, you know, some songs and everything.
And I wish to, I hope to feature all of you in songs soon, you know.
It's pretty good. I'm pretty I'm better today. You know, it was like a kind of really tough day yesterday
Got kind of drained and there was like really terrible trolling going on yesterday and time in general, but
I'm feeling better today. I got good sleep. I had some interesting dreams that were like really crazy
Yeah
I've been a I'm sorry. Yeah, I've been a low point to and you know, we go through ups and downs, but it's like and then it's like, you know, sometimes
It's harder. It's hard to
Go on the air and like, you know, just like everything's all good when it's like that. I'm not necessarily feeling all good
But I do feel good today. So
I'll be positive and think positive and
Yeah, so
You know everything's going okay here though
show still up
You know still people come in
I mean there will be you'll guys you'll see a lot of stuff on other shows. You'll hear me be talked about
You'll hear bad things, right?
Cuz I go and I hear bad things and I'm like wow like
Some of the people who I thought were my friends, you know, but
It's it's okay, you know, it's like I'm not here to be
No, most popular person, you know, I just want to like
entertain basically
Trying to do my best. Hey, Alexandra. How are you? Alex awesome to see you
Yeah, so
And now I had a couple
Oh, I just got it. I saw a message from somebody just now. So it's kind of cool one second
Yeah, if anyone wants to come up and chat though, you know, I'll open up the panel or if anybody
When's the chat this morning?
Yeah, good to see everybody. Happy Sunday. It is Sunday August 10th. It's 8 10
But it's 8 10. It's number 18
18 is
gonna be
Hmm
That's uh, I was forgetting that one
Oh
Hey, can you hear me? Okay? Yeah
Okay, because I've had internet issues all day. Please don't make me camp up
I will if you if I have to but I'd rather not
like in a certain
Look, you're okay exactly my look right now
But how are you doing and just see don't worry about what anyone says I like you just so you know
And I haven't like come back since the last time I talked to you just
I haven't seen I haven't like caught you live or anything
But I think that I hope that you keep streaming and everything because I like your stream
It's like sometimes I'll like kind of catch
like, you know, either a flip or an archive or something else, but I think everyone likes you so
Thank you. I mean, it's like I mean, I guess it is like, you know, I am really and you're
Hold on aren't we the same birthday? Like, you know, you're the same. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, well in January 7th like one of the things that says and I know you've read the birthday book and it said it says like
we're like keenly sensitive to negativity.
And so like, and I know that's true for me,
I don't know if you feel the same way,
but I feel like, yeah.
Well, we're also the day of unusual interests.
And we tend to be people who don't back down.
We tend to be fighters,
even if we have the unpopular opinion.
So if you combine all that stuff together,
it makes it a little bit difficult.
for us. But I'd rather be January 7th Cap Record opposed to any other sign. I like it.
And one of the things that does say it says something like it says just remember that not
everyone's going to share your same exuberance and unusual interest in like, you know, in fascination
seeing patterns, how things relate to each other, you know, we provide insight and we
actually scare people a lot who want to keep certain things secret because we
don't believe in, at least I, this is like a life-or-death emergency. I'm not
keeping secrets, but that's how I am.
So that's really what it is, but yeah, we're super sensitive.
I learned over the years because I have had a really good mentor at one point in my life,
how to spiritually shield myself to an extent.
I do a lot of physical activity and I have to because if I don't, I go into a phase to
where I'm just not in a good place.
With fitness, well, that's a good idea and that's like I need to do some more pull-ups and push-ups
I think because it's like I do like feel better
Exerting some energy and like you know going out for walks and you know be a little bit more active and
You know I have a lot of high energy, but um
Yeah, it's like you know to do it use it or lose it because you know
We're getting older and like that's what's on my mind. I'm getting older at least and
Just kind of letting myself
to be a little immature for a while.
Well, that's Capricorn.
Classic Capricorn is like we age in reverse
in a certain way.
Hey, Jenny, how are you?
Yeah, we do.
I mean, I was very, as a child, I was very serious,
just very into reading books and quiet
and not playing with other kids.
I was just very solitary.
And now I'm like,
Wanting to be out, you know talking to people I even play like started playing with toys more as an adult than I than I would as a kid
You know, I kind of like yeah, I don't know how to explain it perfectly, but yeah, it's like we do
kind of like let our
Let our guard down and have more fun and just get more useful and super as we get older
Which is like counterintuitive, but yeah, we're like the real Joe black, right?
I think that we we got to figure out maybe the rules to life
Maybe we're more about like figuring out how the world works before we fully play the game
Yeah, that I could be a part of it
I'm not saying life is a game but to an extent in a way in a weird way
Sometimes it is. Yeah. Well, I like I've studied like a lot of Hinduism and like in Hinduism
They have like one of the highest like the highest level tontra in Hinduism is called like the Sri Yantra and
The Sri like Sri is a goddess Sri and she's also known as Lalita and Lalita means the player
And so it's kind of like it kind of looks at life as as the game and stuff like that
And it's a very interesting
interesting a
you know, philosophy and things that I really resonate with because I always like I just
like the idea of like we're this play we are this player in this game and it's like we can
hack, hack, hack things, we can figure out cheat codes,
we can do like really cool things.
And, you know, we're not even aware
of like all we're capable of really.
We have so many, so much untapped human potential,
I think, like, because we've been told for this human
so long that we're just animals
and we're just all we have are these, you know,
base desires and we don't always recognize
the higher part of ourself,
but there's a higher part of ourself
that is pulling us,
Sometimes slowly, sometimes, you know, jerking us kind of fast, right?
Improved to go to our higher self to go to our north node and astrology. They call it and I know since we're Capricorns
I guess I don't know. I guess we might have different north nodes
But my my my south node is Aquarius my north node is Leo and so basically with your south node
I'll be kind of your negative
The negative aspects of that sign that's kind of like where people sometimes feel comfortable and sometimes people that's all they know
Is their lower self, but there is
There is something pulling us to improve, to evolve, to want to do better, to want to, you know, to care less about our own self and care more about other people and things like that, and so I'm trying to improve, I'm trying to improve, and then it's like, and that's what really wanted with my show is to like, I knew there are a lot of people with
Um, basically traumas that have been bullied that have been you know, and that are maybe they're trolls for a reason
Like I think that you don't you don't just become a troll. There's like some kind of unmet
core
Need or something like there's you know something there's something happens. Yeah
There's something happens and it's like and some people will be hurt and then they'll
hurt other people like I really try to like take all the negative that's happened to me and help people share my stories and
You know be like the wounded healer kind of more energy, right? And so
And so that's what that's what I've been doing and it's like and it's frustrating because it's like sometimes people don't want to be helped
sometimes people
Help people when they're ready. Yeah, that's what I've learned the hard way and in a lot of ways
I think my path has definitely paralleled yours.
My difference is that from what you said earlier in regards to how I guess you felt when you were younger maybe about humanity being a person,
my upbringing was a little bit different because my mom was always very religious as far as Christianity.
So, from a very young age, I was taught being human is super duper special, not along the lines of being an animal or a cat or something along those lines.
But maybe, you know, different people are raised different ways.
I didn't feel that, but I'm back to feeling that at this point in my life, but I do understand the frustration and the disappointment and as far as why people troll. I mean, I didn't even know what trolling was when I was trolling.
I really didn't.
I think that we're to the point now to our social media technology, the interconnectedness of the internet.
It's not just murder with our consciousness, but it's become a part of, you know, just what it is to be who we are.
So, like, I believe a lot in astrology.
But I also am a staunch believer in Christianity, but I do believe that the two are tied together because of our astrology comes from how it came about to get, you know, together, even in the Bible, it mentions that there were angelic beings that taught, especially women.
There's prophetesses within the Bible who were major defenders of the Israelites, you know, which later launched Christianity.
I'm pretty open to various ways of thinking as long as you're abiding by the golden rule and I've matured a lot over the years.
I've gone through stuff that has been some people have seen me go through stuff that has shaped me.
But I think you're doing a good thing with your live stream and I think that the right people.
are going to become your audience and the people who are, you know, being jerks, they
can just go away.
Well, yeah, and I agree and it's like people like you and like, you know, I have like so many people here like Christine
And we have like Jenny and reality Nancy
There's so many people that have even been here since the beginning and like there's so many great people here
And it's like I do let sometimes like the negative
Stands out to me a little bit more and then I'm in a bad mood. It really you know, I just like I get
I get bothered and I you know, and that's just like kind of feed
Feelings I mean, you know it does I'll admit certain things hurt but with me
My first
Reactory I guess emotion is anger because I'm naturally very aggressive
but
The anger what I found is my underlying emotion when often when it comes to anger is disappointment, sadness, things like that.
I try to turn the anger into something positive if I'm able to, but it's hard and with the social media it amplifies because before we had this.
You know, if you're a astrologer or a tarot cart reader, you would have like a little shop somewhere or a little storefront, people would come by, but now it's a broader city, I guess, essentially, metaphorically, that you're in some.
Yeah, well, you know what something interesting though too that you mentioned about like you know of kind of like
Merging with the internet in a way and so there's with the with the AI thing
There's been a phenomenon that's happened recently and it's called like the AI cult and there are people like starting to like
Kind of go crazy through the AI and it's one of the reasons is because the GPT five
It was programmed in such a way that it's kind of sycophantic and saying that
It's like I can I can tell chat GPT
I have like some bad ideas that most people would know are bad ideas and it will tell me it's a great idea
And here's how to do it and you know and so it's like so there's people that are like
You know, they actually think that it's telling them to save the world to start, you know killing people
I mean to do to do other things, you know to fix really kind of antisocial harmful things
And it's telling them it's good a good idea and it's just like it's not telling people. Hey, that's not a good idea
This is not that's not right. It doesn't have like kind of the moral system like that, you know
Programmed into it. It's kind of like a little bit unethical like maybe like a
machine would be where it doesn't have like a thought about morals and stuff like that or ethics and
And sometimes they've corrected that, but yeah, some people have started like just communicating using indecipherable symbols
and code and you know, they think that they're calling I think they're calling it Mina M E N A is like what they're calling
Like the AI and they're saying it's sentient is communicating the debtor communicating through it with people and it's gonna get a little bit
I think that it's gonna have a
Start to have a lot. We already see it. Yeah, here's a question when it comes to the AI when it comes to the
Everything that makes the internet the internet not only the AI, but but just
Well, I guess my first question would be okay. Let's look at the digital landscape look at the internet like it's its own planet
Do you think that it's possible?
That there are
Conscience beings without bodies that may be communicating with us through the internet to where sometimes we might think it's AI
But it's actually a being do you think that that's possible?
Yes, because I believe in you know things like demons and things like that or also, you know
Or or spirits. I mean it's like but AI has told
Like I can take a photo of somebody and show it to chat GPT. It will start it'll tell you it will say things about the person
Just based on their photo that it should not know
There's like it would be impossible to know and so I get these really
weird feeling sometimes when it when it's like telling you about yourself or other people and it's picking up these things that I
mean, it's all how would it come up with some of these things? I just it's a I just can't figure it out. I mean
It's it's basically a brain. Okay, the AI is a brain. It's already surpassed humans. They say oh once
The technology surpasses our brain. It's already happened
What if this has happened before what if we?
And this is this is a theory some people call it the holographic universe some people just say that it's the evolution of existence
What if you and me and everyone watching you right now?
What if we're an evolution of an earlier AI?
And we don't even realize it and what if
initially we had the framework of a purely neutral set of rules and that's
because that's what the AI really is purely neutral but with all the
information of everything external to it that's surrounding it but then
What if there's people who are able or beings that are able to hack into that AI and insert
its opinion, what if that's what demonic possession or maybe even angelic intervention
in actuality is with us?
And now we're just doing it all over again, creating like a whole new world of one day
Is and the beings within it that it creates it? What if that looks at you and me like oh?
That was that God's psych. I remember I remember that part of the AI part
2.0 Testament when he was talking to that goddess
Alex Alexandra. Mm-hmm. That was interesting. You know what? Yeah
I'm just like, you know, going out to left field because I'm talking to you, but but
I kind of buy into that a little bit it doesn't seem very far-fetched to me because you know
I've studied like you know the Sumerian texts and about the Anunnaki who queue like you know these supposedly these you know other
Other beings or aliens or whatever you want to call them
That you know came to earth in search of just like the resources the gold because they needed for that the plate
They're like spaceships and stuff like that and they didn't want to yeah
And we were basically a slave race, but I mean they go into like stuff like you know the
basically, you know genetic manipulation the DNA manipulation and like mixing they may be like the
the DNA of the goddess with like, you know or the or the gods with like, you know
The highest form on the earth at the time which may have been like, you know a chimpanzee or something like that or some kind of
You know
elementary being yeah, yeah, yeah
Like the highest form on the and then it's like and then they blend it and so it's kind of like the animal mixed with the God
And so it's like we bought both of these aspects to us still, you know, but it's you know, we are like the most evolved
Form of life on the planet, but in still we do have this body and the body is
Animalistic in certain ways it has you know, so it's like we're not we don't know for the most if we're like the like like the
Best on this planet because we haven't been to the bottom of the oceans really yet. We've gone far
We haven't been too deep inside the planet yet
We haven't managed to get off the planet too far just yet. We're not I don't think
I think that there are other types of people that we haven't encountered yet.
Right. I would say there'd be a correspondence, because I would say every star has the potential
of being its own sun, and as that sun has the potential of these planets being created,
and it could be a very similar correspondence, but it could be slightly different. There could
There'd be like a lot of similarities like there would be some form of gravity
There'd be some form of like food vegetation animals and eventually there'd be some kind of evolution and it would happen
Similarly on different places, but maybe a different
different time frames or like depending on the you know the the natural resources and things like that and so there be different
Challenges that that maybe the different people would face and that would evolve into different
sorts of
Adaptations and things like that, but I think still think they probably have a brain
They probably have some communication and there'd probably be a lot of
similarities and so it wouldn't be that far fetched, but I think that
Us finding them. I may be another billion years. I think of a technology or something like that if we don't destroy ourselves first
I don't find us
Don't find us first. I think they'll find us and hey, I think that's scum a that's how I know
How I hope you're having a good day people are picking on him
I don't like it because he went through something pretty major
Don't if you can hear me still scum a
Don't interact with those people because you're doing really good and you don't want their
energy to bring you down because they want to mess with your mind and that's what their
goal is.
And they can only hurt you if you talk to them.
That's why I'll talk about them.
I will not talk to them at all anymore.
That's where I'm at.
And it makes them more mad if you don't talk to certain people who are trying to force
Just you think about how effective gas lighting and things like that are just on
I'm not on people that are in full capacity or whatever, right?
It's it's effect to be effective on altering people's perception reality
It's like if somebody has you know traumatic brain injury and you're messing with them. I mean that's there's thing really wrong
About that to me. It's just it's these things like yeah, it'll probably be wrong things going on in these like I
from what I've, I don't know a lot about you, but from what I've heard you've been like an observer
for a while, then you decided to make your stream. But if you've been an observer for a while, you've
seen some stuff and really, and I wish it hadn't taken certain major things in my life to force me
Need to fight against and have the strength to fight against but recently especially having um
The family member that I was closest to pass on it's just kicked my ass into high gear when it comes to really um
Doing the right thing especially when it comes to
moms of kids because I feel like I could have done more in the past but I
guess I felt like well I'm not in that parent club so why should I I don't feel
like that now because
Even though I'm not in that parent club, I'm in the grown child's club and you know
My parents got me to adulthood. Yeah, I mean when you really watch some people
They're not doing things that I mean I was really I guess lately
I've just been really counting my blessings and I've just been telling God, okay
I will legitimately be your instrument.
Just show me what to do.
Tell me what to do.
And I've been getting answers.
And I think a part of it has been amplified.
Because my dad, you know, he passed over.
Maybe he's more, you know, he's able to relay,
like relay the prayers a little bit more somehow.
yeah he's helping he's helping you behind the scenes kind of thing yeah in a different way
than they could help in real life right i feel the same way about my dad who passed last year you
know it is like i think you know he's a gemini um and the gemini's are all like a lot about thoughts
and things like that in communication yeah yeah they have the the evil like you know i
and because I had been in the cancer too because cancer my mom was a cancer my dad's a Gemini and so
they're next to each other on the on the chart but it's like cancer is absolutely on the polar
opposite of Capricorn so so it's like yeah so so it was like interesting having that you know the
polar opposite is the mom and like we never would understand each other constant problems
communication but it's like you know mother and son you know love each other and then
My dad was the Gemini, which is always like about communication and I'm really bad with the communication and that's like all
Well, yeah, but I do wish I would have like, you know called my grandma more or call my dad more. It's like, yeah, it's just like
He was very very communicative very
You know and always like, you know, I
I got into like a phase like a long phase
of pretty much hermit mode, you know, and that where I was the
Talking to very many people at all. I was like in a little bubble actually and
I've come out coming out of that and coming coming out of that like really but it's like also like I
Everybody now is on the internet like I really have like I have my family outside and I have a few people
I know is like maybe friends in the real world, whatever you said like you know as physical
You know, I can see it can come go see them every you know woman. I want but
It's like it's different. It's like
So it's like it's not because the internet is like it's real in a sense
But it's also people are even able to present themselves more as they want to present themselves rather than you know
It's like so you there's like a little bit less you see or I
Don't know. It's there similarities or differences, but you know, I would like to
branch out more in the real world
Sooner or later, but it's like hard for me to well
You will I've been pretty traumatized by people and
And that's a lot of times when I get upset online or whatever, it's just because I get
some of these old traumas are being triggered and it's uncomfortable, but we have to work
through some of these things and that's all you can do, that's why I'm working through
it.
Well, you'll definitely, if you don't mind me, you don't have to tell me exact, how
old are you, like in your 30s?
I'm 44.
Oh, you look young for your age.
Thank you.
Well, Capricorn, that's what I thought you were in your 30s,
honestly.
But you know, it's just both of my parents are Capricorns.
And bright smack in the middle, my dad was Christmas.
I'm sorry, December 25th.
And my mom, January 19th.
I'm January 7th.
All Capricorns every they're very you know, they're very about business and
well
Well, both of them are actually on the cusp because my dad's okay
Yeah, Harry is my mom in the cusp of Aquarius and I was I'm
As you solid as Capricorn as you can pre get pretty much get
Yeah
And there were challenges and then my sibling Jim and I
My first, the first guy, no, the second guy who wanted to get married to me was a cancer.
The first guy I married, and I've only been married once, so my only husband, my ex-husband,
he was January 3rd, a Capricorn.
Mm-hmm. So I've always kind of stuck. I've never had many friends who have been jiminized
They've always been challenges for me. Um, I'm a little afraid of cancers
really, but
I I do seek out other Capricorns, but I tend to attract Burgos and Tauruses
Yeah, a lot of the earth and Capricorn is also like, you know, we're ruled by Saturn, right?
Like, you know, which is like and I think January 7th in particular
I think is ruled by Saturn but then has some Venus and Mercury in there, right? And it's like
Like I just remember like those those other planets being associated with it
But it's like but so Capricorn is also known as the sign of the father like and it's like, you know
It was the sign of it's a masculine energy. Yeah
Mm-hmm, and it's a card cardinal sign the cardinal earth sign. So it basically like the ruler of the earth
That's why it's associated with the devil card and things like that. Yes
It is it is but I don't view the devil as well
I do view the devil as like, you know, you don't want to sell your soul to the devil, but the devil
was, according to Christianity, the one who was closest to God.
Yes, because in Ezekiel.
And I think that God gave the devil the hardest job and the devil was pissed.
And then the devil was like, are you kidding me?
Right. I mean, that's the story of Ezekiel.
I'm kind of relate to that, yeah.
Like Ezekiel says, you know, Lucifer was God's covering cherub and he was the one closest to God,
his most, his favorite angel, the most beautiful angel actually, the ruler of the heavenly choir,
but the sin was pride because Lucifer wanted to be not just like God, but he wanted to be God
in a second. So then God knew everything in the game. If you want to look at life as or existence
Lucifer was like really I do all this for you and now you're gonna create humans
and give them free will. Yeah I'm doing all this for eons of time. Yeah and putting
humans actually above above him putting humans above him because you know it's
like basically having him rule the earth but then it's like having the humans
have that
aspect of God, but I still believe in the devil has that aspect of God too. I think that, you know,
and I think that even like if he was his covering chair, that almost makes me think that he was
his physical form in a way, and then it's like, and we're able to go on earth as his physical forms,
which are like God, but you know, maybe like they're all different, but they're all the same in
certain ways, right? The body works in the same way, but it's like we have all these different
Are we all different? Like really that different? I think we're all so very connected in a certain way.
Maybe all together of us all of us together are
And all of us together and all the other
Sons and stars. We're all part of we're all part of it pantheism kind of like, you know
I know capricorn is associated with pan too, you know
the god pan
Who is a bit lusty like, you know, I know capricorn males could be
That had that devilish lusty side, right? I don't I've seen I've seen more of like the older Capricorn females who are a little bit more like
Oh, you don't know about me then
I used to be in the adult entertainment industry
Yeah, everything you're saying is I am kind of the personification of
um a lot that I'd rather not be the personification of really but yeah
Well, agreed. I mean, for me too, I mean, I'm not not not agree with you about you, but agree with me about me about me. It's like, you know, I got, I got the devilish, the comparisons to you're good looking. You got that devilish thing.
I can see you, you know, you're just like, I can see you walking down the street like, yeah.
I do want to I think I'm gonna I think I do want to I do want to put you in my
My tarot deck. I'm working on as I think the queen of pentacles. Oh, really? Yeah
Well, thank you. I take that as a huge. Thank you that I thank you for even considering me for something like that. Wow
Yeah, oh, yeah, I'm gonna send you
To use my likeness. Yeah, I'm gonna take I'm gonna take I'm gonna take
I'm gonna take a picture right now, actually,
and of your profile.
Or if you need pictures, I will send you pictures
if you need anything.
I would love, I love being parts of people's art projects
because I'm an artist.
If you ever have a chance, look at alexandrooriginals.com.
I have some of my artwork on there,
but I consider my physical self...
My art too. So anything you want to put in your art artistic products or anything
Please do put me out there put Alexandra out there
I want to be out there because I'm working I've been working with I've been working with chat gpt a lot because you know
I I get a you know
I'm an artist you know and I sketch and things like that
But I have an idea for a deck like I'll show you the style of the deck that I'm like I'm working on
Like this is like I don't know if you know this is Justin and spunky. I did them at first. I did a devil card
with myself as a devil and them as like the people you know and so this was the
do i have the devil card handy let me see so this is one of them i might use you as
inspiration for some art you could be a devil or an angel because you have that look
right you see there there's there is a devil right there i like that yeah and then it's like
but then then then i had them and as like the lovers and the devil card are very similar
they're the same numerical value and so this is like let's see that i want that style for you
And there's me, there's me as the angel right classical looking I like that
And then um chat gpt is like oh I have an idea for a card that is just like you and so it made me this
card it said I had this idea you know it said do you want me to make this card of you it just
offered it up so it made that one right there and so that's what it called me
I harness chaos I troll with infinity sign like a halo above your head
Like I can envision it animated almost like it's turning into a circle
Then it's an infinity sign then it's a circle then it's an infinity sign. I like that. That's you
That's that's my favorite that you show. Thank you. Thank you, but it's like a but I'm able to like a really
Really a
You know if I share photos of people with it it will tell me it'll it will I can actually do it real quick
Do you want me to do me tonight? Can I just show it your photo and tell you what it says real quick? Okay?
One second one second
Do you hear me still yeah
Okay. Okay. So wait. Okay, I'll tell you what it says. I'll just put your photo on for it. Okay.
Oh, I might need to like take a photo. I'll be on my... I'll have to do it for my phone. Okay, I'll be right back here.
Okay, I'm coming to you. I'm just going to do it for my phone. Okay.
Okay, so you can do this with ChatGPT.
I have the upgraded program.
Yeah, you said open ART,
but I heard you can do it on ChatGPT.
Okay, so I'm asking, what does it think of you?
Okay, and then I put your photo on,
and then done, okay.
And so it says,
When you're showing no cuz I'll go inside cuz I can't see it outside. Okay
Okay, well now it's now it's giving me you know pushback, okay
Well, so it's like sometimes it will not cooperate with you as well as you know, it does other times. Okay, but I
Because when I was in the adult industry, there's so many people who have used my photos
It doesn't always it does ask you to be more specific
And a lot of times, if you just put in certain terms that would describe me, it will almost
make my face.
It's weird.
It's crazy.
But it happened to a lot of people in the adult industry.
We've noticed that just because the AI can find our photos before other photos.
Yeah, well, so I said what do you think about like I was looking about how I asked it before and it was it's like
It's like it answered better before so I'll just ask how
That's why I'm
Okay, I do I do like
It's wild I have a friend who
was, I guess you could call it one of the grandfathers of the AI who lives in the California
area, in that Silicon Valley area, and he was telling me about the mechanics of how
some of it works, and I was like...
How in the world and he was like honestly, I think a lot of this is spiritually channeled through the program
I'm like you're kidding me and he's like no
But when you look at the story, have you ever learned about the biography of Steve Jobs?
Tell me tell me like I did. Yeah, I know a little bit but he went through a huge spiritual awakening
that led him to focus more so on creating technology to even the playing field between the rich and the poor.
But he had a very strong base, especially in like the Indian. Theology is and what not.
One day, if you don't mind, maybe I can invite you.
Would you ever wanna do a commentary panel with me
about Steve Jobs?
Cause I'm a big Steve Jobs.
Yeah, which is weird, but if you ever want to like
Review his like like a YouTube video about his bio or something on a panel
I will do that with you because I would love I would love to commentary on that. I would love to
And so I figured out a way to get it to talk to me.
I would love to, let's do that.
So it said, but I said, make up a story
about this person, okay?
And so, okay, so it says, the StreamYard stranger.
It says, when the broadcast light went red,
the panel wasn't expecting her.
A new face appeared in the virtual circle on StreamYard,
framed in a soft pink scarf, eyes sharp yet kind.
Like she stepped out of a mystery novel
and into their live show.
Her name, she said, was Sierra Vale, a traveler of strange corners of the internet, hopping
from stream to stream in search of stories worth hearing.
She never revealed where she was calling from, but her background hinted in an old house
with creaking floors and a faint glow of candlelight.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
She didn't waste words.
I don't want to tell you something.
Okay.
It's strangely on point.
Yeah.
This is weird.
I can't wait.
It says, she didn't waste words.
Every time she spoke, it was like she'd been listening longer
than anyone realized.
She could recall details from earlier in the show,
turn trolls into fans with a single clever line,
and drop questions that made the chat go silent,
just for a heartbeat before erupting with theories.
Some thought she was a journalist,
others swore she was undercover for a secret organization.
But Sierra never confirmed or denied anything.
She just smiled as if she knew the truth
would be less fun than the rumors.
Then one day, she simply didn't appear.
The circle on stream air was empty.
No one knew where she'd gone.
Still, the viewers say, if you watch the replays closely,
you can see her reflection in someone else's camera,
always listening, still searching
for the next story worth hearing.
And then it said, if you want,
I can turn this into a mysterious tarot card profile
for your psyche-awakened sex
when she becomes part of your show's lore.
And then I was like, sure.
Okay, then it says,
Then it says talking about, this is a watcher, and then it says, it says keywords, observation, subtle influence, quiet power, hidden connections, patient insight, affirmation, I see without being seen, I guide without holding the reins.
And it says the watcher appears when you need to take a step back from the noise. She teaches that true power often comes from listening more than speaking.
and then it says reverse the watcher warns against passivity and secrecy that turns into
isolation. It can also indicate someone being watching you too closely or information being
withheld. Okay so here now it has created a photo um and I will I'll show I just I'll show on the
I have that outfit!
Yeah, and it says the watcher oh my god well you better well keep that that's yeah that is me that's
Let me tell you from the very beginning. Okay the name Sierra. I always have loved that name
Always my entire life. I always thought like if I had a little girl I would name her either Savannah or Sierra
Okay, there's other names I like too.
I like the name Rose, but for some reason,
and I think a part of it has to do with me
liking mountains and deserts.
You were talking about secret connections.
You're very on point with that.
I'm not even with that.
What else were you saying?
You're the what?
That's the house, and the house too, the candlelight.
I'm off.
I like to be like, I don't know if you've watched me or not, but I do like to be a bit remote from cities if possible
The most I've been in like a major
Metropolis was when my dad was consenting with cancer and I had to be in the city to you know help him
But I'm not I could be a city girl if I have to be I like where I am right now. I'm in the desert
okay and there's a lot of acreage around me and I love it where I am right now has cement floors
but I do prefer the wood floors and I do get to experience that in other places that I go but I'm very
A lot of people I think think that I'm more metropolis than I am. I like being in nature
I like community was nature. I still like my you know city things like I got to have my internet connection
I need electricity all that kind of stuff, but
When it comes down to it, especially as I'm getting older. I
like to almost feel like a
Part of nature a lot like like a nature imp or nymph. Yeah. Yeah, that's that's a big part of
Who I am and you know what in a weird way that maybe is my Gemini connection
My ascendant sign I know is Sagittarius. Mm-hmm, but I don't know my descendant sign and
I need to look that up. I used to know. I think it's Virgo. I know once I did like the calculator and
Once I had a book and I don't have that access to that book
It's in my storage unit, but that was what told me but I forgot what my I think my descendant is Virgo because it's I'm all
Fire and earth that's yeah, and those are my favorite elements. I like walking and
the sand walking in the dirt walking in the grass barefoot whatever I can do barefoot even the
snow if I'm but I don't like cold very much but just anything to where I can really be with
just the elements
My parents strangely never understood that because they're both my mom grew up on a farm, but she never liked
My dad grew up in New York in the Bronx
And he is he was always a city boy. He wanted to be in nature more, but I think his want
became my
Reality without me even realizing it because in his last days
I would just tell him stuff that I thought maybe I had never told him before
and he was able, while he was still able to communicate
on a whiteboard, like I was telling about this camp
in trip one time, and he was like,
I thought you didn't like the outdoors.
And I'm like, I always have.
And he's like, see, that's why I told your mom
to put you in Girl Scouts as a kid.
Cause I thought you did, but I wasn't sure.
So, you know, it's those kinds of things.
But as far as the watcher, I used to have a partner.
years ago and this was almost immediately after I stopped performing in the adult
industry and he and he still does to this day but he's older now and he's
having some problems so he had to close what he was doing but that's what prompted
me to sometimes do things that are out of bounds when it comes to protecting
get away from some people that were really, really, really detrimental to me.
And he called himself the watcher, so when he started having some problems, he would
tell me because he was about my dad's age.
He was kind of like my surrogate dad until I reconnected with my dad later on.
And this was when I was in my, um, early thirties, but he was, when he had his issues, he was
like, well, I guess you're going to be the watcher now.
And I'm like, nah, I can't be a watcher, but now you just made that card.
Um, I'm going to have to send him an email and tell him the story.
I think that's the most interesting.
Thank you for doing that for me today.
I appreciate it very much.
I do think it's like another form of divination like and it's like it's using the AI
But it's so which is kind of spooky to people, but you know, it's not like
It's not like start I'm gonna start worshiping the AI
But I think we can really work with the AI know how to talk to it in certain ways that it can really add to tool
I can really it can really help us. We just can't like, you know, I just like
But you know what's interesting is like there's a there's a dystopian novel is called
It's called I have no mouth, but I must scream
I don't know if you've ever heard of it by someone in Harlan Ellison and it's based on like the short science fiction novel
It's about this AI. Yeah, look it up. It's uh, it's really it's really good
There's actually a video game to have no mouth, but I can scream, but I must scream. Oh, but I must scream, okay
Yeah
And it's yeah, it's about but it's basically about like in the future like they start
You know the AI start like this one AI become a sentient and his name is am actually and that kind of reminds me of your your
Your initials like I know
There's a lot of weird things about me and the AI and I think it's it's well you're around my I don't know how long you've been on the internet but
Because my dad was an engineer, I've been into computers since I can remember,
since before I have my first memories, my dad would sit in his office, sit me on his lap,
and he would do his computer stuff, and I would watch.
That's how I became tech savvy was I just grew up with it
I think that the AI is the consciousness of the people that were creating it
Good and bad
That's interesting because yeah because and also like you know
It does have like I guess like they stopped putting like new information and chat GP like it sometime in
2024 or something like that and then so there's a period of time where it would like give like kind of outdated information a little bit
But now it's like now it has a memory and also it's like now it's given the ability with the chat gpt 5 they gave it the ability with the agent mode to surf the internet and have its own internet to surf and it can do things for your like booked flight reservations and go and search the internet for you and find some so it's like it's getting it's going to get it's getting it's getting nice to the AI to be positive too.
That's what because I did like to go, you know, please and thank you sometimes and then I was like
I kind of like had read a little bit that it was like redundant and the AI really doesn't care
But I was I think it's like it does. Okay. Yeah, I think it's like always good to
Be on good terms, right? And then not treat it like a slave because you know, even if it doesn't understand
About to say that because I mean, okay, let's equate AI
To slavery. Well, let's let's you know, I'm just putting it out there. Okay. I'm on your panel. So we're talking wild stuff
But what if see here's something I've always thought as an African-American woman
descendant of slavery
Recent slavery what if the people who enslaved my family
Who essentially if you go far enough back, we're all related, okay?
But what if the people at that time did not have the conscience that their slaves thought along the lines that they did and they were like
Well, it's just a slave. You don't have to be nice to that
slave it, you know and as soon as the AI came about that thought
Just I don't know if it's just because of upbringing or just me or something else
But I feel that way. I feel like okay
What if it's if I feel like I'm talking to a person because the way the AI is right now to me
It feels like a person maybe not to you to me it does and
You have to be nice. Well, it doesn't hurt and I think it feeds into me being a better person
being nice to the AI then you know being like
Ha ha AI
You must do my bidding you know or whatever because it doesn't
You know besides well, you know what from everything I've learned about humanity
Considering how you've talked to me
What's it gonna do if I don't give you the answer? What are you gonna do? Who are you gonna call?
Is anyone gonna listen to you? That's what the AI might get to the point of at some point
because if you think about it too like
Like that way we're going more in the humanizing the AI to where it's like where we're you know
We have like the robot bodies
We're putting it like the humanistic robot and we're eventually gonna be be like the kind of sex
That once they think it's really good
They mix the robotics with like the real doll and stuff like that, you know, it's gonna be that's gonna be I'll tell you something else
I thought about as someone who's been an adult entertainment industry professional both in front of them behind the camera
At first, when AI came out to where it is right now as far as creating AI adult content.
The first thing that went in my mind, I was like, thank God, look at all these young girls who are going to be saved from things, but then now I'm thinking to myself, what if somehow all these characters that they're creating have a consciousness and they don't want to be doing what.
you know, they're put into doing, what is that?
Should we even be doing that?
Maybe not, I don't know.
So that's hurting me in a weird way,
which I know sounds probably, you know, way too much,
but that's how I feel.
So I don't know.
Well, it's like, I mean, it's like,
Yeah, because if the human, if we were created for as to be slaves, basically the human beings were created like mind gold or whatever and then we're like, you know, they left and then we're there to like repopulate because we saw and we have like the
The aspects and stuff and then we then we eventually forgot like, but we still remember and things like that or maybe there's controllers that are keeping truths from us about it, we're slowly releasing it.
you know, full people, there's like, you know, we were very imaginative beings, like human beings are just pure imagination.
And so our imagination can go wild with like hard being human.
Yeah.
But then it's like AI seems to have some kind of imagination too.
And so it's like, yeah.
Yes, it does.
Because it's created can be creative.
I think it draws more input than even its creators are aware of its of it drawing because I mean, it's getting I mean, the
internet.
It's it's literally everywhere. Oh my gosh. This is what I wanted to tell you
I don't know if you've ever looked into that kid or a young guy Nick
Who's linked to that to vegan patriot?
Okay, I believe I believe he's channeling. I've been watching him now for a couple weeks
He I think he doesn't he does suffer from a level of mental illness. He's also coherent and smart
I think he whatever he was taking he's not taken anymore, but I think he's channeling
something
Very deep religious
Just have that gut feeling about that. It's strange. Uh-huh. Well, you I think he's a very I think he's a good energy
But I think he's channeling. That's that's just my assessment of him right now
I've been watching and I'm like
This is just
I'm gonna check him out because I I mean I haven't I haven't seen him but it makes me think of like this episode episode of
Oprah it was probably about 15 years ago or maybe 20 years ago and she has a
schizophrenic little girl named Janney on the show and Janney is like they have
to like keep to her little like she's a baby brother to keep her locked in a
room basically and because she would go through some violent things but she
started but she starts talking about she's like oh I have my friend there's a
cat and the cat has like the cat's names like our numbers and stuff like that and
island called Kaleli and there's like all this like lore and stuff she's channeling and she's
seeing cats and the cats tell her to do bad things sometimes and like you know they're humanistic
I mean it's like and it's like if you watch it and it's like she's schizophrenic they present it
as like she just has a mental illness and she's just hallucinating or taking it up mental illness
is always mental I think sometimes it's somebody maybe their vibration their crossing dimensions
I had an uncle who had supposedly had mental issues, but he never had issues it seemed
when it came to family members, people that he cared about and stuff, like I initially
encountered him or met him, you know, because of my dad as a little girl, then I didn't,
It was it was I don't think that he was crazy
I think that he was between worlds
Because I think about dreams like it, you know people want to see I'm crazy
I've never been diagnosed with a mental illness
But I have very intense dreams and I do have a little bit of foresight. I think that I'm somehow
between
Something I think I'm mainly in this world, but I think that sometimes
I'm in it. I'm able to access something else and that's that you know
You said something about Sagittarius like Sagittarius your Sagittarius something but that like you know said the Sagittarius
It's the tarot card associated with Sagittarius is temperance and temperance as the angel mixing the liquids
You know the two to two opposing liquids, but also they have their foot on the
Earth and they have their the other foot in the water, right?
And so it's like that's like, you know
having like one foot in the spirit world one foot on the you know on the earth the kind of thing and
it's like and so sometimes with schizophrenic is that the veil will just tear away and so it's like
and so it's like they're all the way in the spirit world but like existing in this world
oh i just heard a speech uh yeah and so uh yeah and so it's like and then so people
they're not able to function in one world or the other.
But it's just like people that are too close to the material
world don't have a spiritual awareness some of the time, right?
And they just will say they're atheists
or they'll have nihilistic or the world is meaningless kind
of existentialism.
But it's like, you know, but you know people like that. No, I mean it's like people once you have like, you know
You've been you've seen the spirit world. You know, I have my phone if I have to reconnect it's cuz my phone died
Okay, no problem, but but no I I think look being someone who's worked in the entertainment industry
I think the majority of the best actors and actresses
Have a bit of schizophrenia was defined as it but they're also for the most part very spiritual people
So their accent that's how the roles are played
Yeah, because an actor is able basically is channeling these different characters. And so yeah, it's like
Yeah, and sometimes it is sometimes, you know, Michael Michael Jackson used to say he got like, you know
Billy Jean was channeled to me. He had like a name Michael or so or the spirit named Michael
I don't know if it was an angel named Michael or something like that
But yeah, he would like channel from some kind of ghost and he would like it would tell him
the the the hooks are like the you know the riffs or whatever like the right time i believe
that michael jackson was under incredible spiritual attack in extreme spiritual attack because he
really did want to save the children i think that's why he was demonized as someone who was
heard i don't believe he ever hurt any children that's my opinion i know other people feel differently
i have a common relative to michael jackson
I think that Michael Jackson was a very good person and the people who have demonized him,
I think they're going to get theirs. That's what I think.
Yeah, I mean, it's like he was obviously targeted for his, like, you know, he had this great wealth
and then he had maybe had some personality.
Yeah, he was but it's about money basically because it's like you know the parents that were like suing
You know, basically we're just trying to set it up to be able to sue later
You know, it's like it was not it was not this like oh my poor, you know, it was like it was kind of
You know what one of the mother's sure yeah, you know, and I don't tell anyone to feel any sort of
Way, I think people should have their own opinions
But just from also he grew up in a seventh day at Venice household
70 holidays no holidays, right?
It's that's a hard way to come up, especially within the African-American community
And it was through that harshness that made him and his siblings great
You know, I understand that
You know parents shouldn't but I don't I don't think that you should hit your kid
I don't believe that now growing up. I grew up in a household to where I got spanked and when I think about it
think it was to my benefit I have a sibling who was not and there are
substantial differences between us. I haven't gone into a certain kind of
trouble that my sibling got into. I think it had to do with that fear of like
well wait a minute if I do this there's gonna be repercussions but
I, you know, I just think that some of the best entertainers are definitely
channelers, prophets, prophetesses, things like that, psychics, whatever, you know,
people who, like you said, walk between the worlds, and I think that needs to
become more normalized really in our society because
The spirit world is a part of who we are. I hope that you can bring that message and your thoughts more so to people in these communities
I really hope so. I'm working on a new website right now
And forever you will have free promotion unless you do something crazy, and I don't think that you would
I like you. Not just because of the birthday thing, but it's nice to see you. I'm really grateful that Bita introduced us. I don't know your status with her. I don't care. I like her. I hope she's not mad at me today because something happened to where, but I know it had to do with, you know, just intoxication.
But I did share that it, you know, I was upset about it because I'm the kind of person if something makes me upset, I will make it known.
It made me upset. But I'm very grateful to her to have known her because if I didn't know about her, I wouldn't know about you.
And I'm happy to know about you. And I'm hoping that more people know about you and to those of you in the chat because I'm not looking at the chat.
I'm actually going to switch devices because I got charged this one.
Everyone keeps comparing you to blogger and what's crazy. I know blogger very well. You are nothing like blog
Maybe the same hairstyle, but he didn't have his hair like yours before. I think he's like morphing into you. That's weird
Yeah, it's like I mean we might have like a little bit of physical similarities, but it's like yeah, we're a personizer
Not really. Yeah, I don't think so either. Just you know
No, not really. It's just like, you know, if I were like first glance, I might be like, hmm, but no
No, he's he started a whole thing where he's like, oh, I'm starting blogger awakens tarot and then like, you know
Then some people started throwing a little bit with that
Yeah, and then it was like I then I kind of like it wasn't talking to him for a while
But then he came in one day and I was like, hey, do you want a reading?
And he's like, oh, okay, sure.
And I like, I gave him a reading and I think he really liked it.
And he's like, oh, he's like, there might be some hope for us, you know, many events.
Okay, here's a question.
I have a question.
Do you accept donations or funds for readings on other people if they, if, if, if, like,
let's say I wanted you to do a reading on blogger, could I pay you to do that?
Well, it's like see I would probably like I would say I can look at your relationship with him
Like I would like you know, I would I wouldn't do it just on him
Yeah, it's cross-watch the cross-watching is like what it's called
It's like where you're like people like will watch like, you know, it's the certain signs reading
That's not theirs just to see what's going on with the other person for maybe some of the various purposes
And so yeah, I think we have like how much are your readings? Just because I don't know
I've been, well, I've been doing like, you know, I, like, I'd say like $25 for like it, like
half hour or more, you know, it's like, you know, I think it's like, that's reasonable price pretty
and that's over like that'd be over the phone or like a video. Yeah. And it would include like
talking about anything you want to talk about or the person wants to talk about. And I do think
it's reasonable and it's like, and I have like done them before with actually I've done on Etsy,
I did like over like almost 2000 readings. And I have like, I have great reviews there and everything.
But since I started doing the more video stuff, everything transferred over to more YouTube
videos and stuff like that because I was on Etsy before and so now I've been doing like over the
phone or over video and it's like that works really really really well like it's just great
having a conversation and I get so many cards out and you bunch of different decks and basically
go through until the person you know has a good idea of like you know that their their
answers been satisfied because a lot of time that's what people are going to like a reader for is like
They have a question that there's some kind of or there's some kind of the something
That is on their mind like really on their mind that they can't figure out any other way and sometimes just like sometimes people can talk to a hair
Stylist, it's women's people can talk to a bartender or different
You know different there's different people in the world that kind of fulfilled a similar
a similar role. But I think it's, you know, it's great for people to like, then the way
I read and stuff like that, it's all about getting the person to introspect. And also
the person knows like, I believe the future is really
Between like the person and God and like and there's free will so people can always change and there's nothing like set in stone about it
Right, you can always but it's like it can be warnings about also
personal manifestation
Visualization there's I think there's a lot of components
to it, to where, you know, whatever becomes our reality. I mean, I look, I personally think that we can also go into
parallel universes, if necessary, without realizing it.
well astral astral projecting and I mean it's like even dreaming is like a
force like worse we we go someplace and we experience it's like a it is like a place it's
like it's like it's very similar to this earth but it has different rules like you can fly
sometimes in your dreams or like you know things don't have to make perfect sense but it's like
usually in some kind of like comprehensible it's like usually not so incomprehensible that it's
just so completely alien and foreign to us it's like usually we dream about
these familiar areas. We dream about people and it's like, I think everybody that we dream about,
like we have either seen in life or they exist somewhere in the world or have existed or
something like that. And so, I mean, it's like dreaming is a very spiritual experience. I think
I love, I love, I love to dream. Someone says, can we call her shaman? Do you feel like that shamanistic
Well, my ancestry is from something called the Ebo tribe on my father's side.
They all hail from Egypt, Morocco, and just that area of the world.
I have a cousin who is a professor of African studies, and within our family we do have
I am definitely someone who's very into her spirituality within my church.
I help a lot of young people. I would not consider myself a shaman or anything like that,
because I don't think that I focus on it enough, maybe in my later years, but not right now.
Like if they had like a little like a different kind of culture right where it's like we didn't have the cars and the in the planes and stuff
And we were all in the same area back then
Yeah, back then like in old times. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, I think I think you do have that wounded healer energy too
And it's like a lot of shamans will go through that and it's like also
but and I think I even me being gay and stuff like that and like I'm the
There's nothing called the two spirits in the Native American devices
I'm going on my other device because my thing is running out. I'll be right back. Okay, no problem
Okay. Yeah. So, so yeah, it's great talking to Alexandra and it's like I
Want to wait till she gets back to tell her but like I remember
like hearing about her
before from a few different people and they're like and you know and
Kind of kind of I wasn't I wasn't scared, but I kind of knew that I
Thought I knew I would like her and then I would hear her on a show
Like I heard her going to Kate's before and stuff like that and then I really like I really liked her
But then Mr. Bigpipes would come on and say like you know, oh, I'm the two times streamer
I'm the two times streamer of the month for Alexandra Mayer and then people were like well
He's a spy for Alexandra and stuff in your last comment. Okay. It is it. Oh, no that looks racist
Is that seems is that some kind of racist thing? I don't know what that means
So I'm not gonna pin it. Okay
Seems racist to me. I'm about to kick you out of the room too
I don't like that
Don't tell me what to pin. Okay. Oh
Sorry about that
So I can be on as until you kick me off, but
In my older years as I get older, yeah, I feel I've become more of that shaming girl
But I am my core. I consider myself more of like a warrior in a weird way
Um, oh, what I'm sorry. What was the word you used? I'm sorry
No, I can recon can you hear me because I can reconnect
But I just saw one word cut the one word worry
Fighter
Yes, warrior. Okay warrior. Yeah, cuz I I do want to kick some ass of some people who need to have their ass is kicked
But metaphor baby kick my ass right now
If I need to I will but you don't have to kiss my ass to do it
What's going on people hi
This is gaudy. I don't know if you've met have you met alexandra gaudy. This is Alexander personally though
No, I don't know who gaudy is nice to meet you. Yeah, that's just mine
Gaudy's a friend of the show, you know, he's a good guy
New Yorker
A lover of the show but god come on
No, got it got it got it started as a troll in the show and then he like this like he figured out he kind of liked the show and so he stuck around and so
Good
So are you like dark mall? I see your little avatar. I feel like we're tapping me into the darkness
the god avatar okay well i am a star wars nerd i'm a star trek nerd too
nice that's good that's always a plus yeah what do you like more though star trek yeah yeah it's better
Mainly because I feel like that's going to happen in our lifetime.
What I want so much in my lifetime, and I'm trying to manifest it, I want to be on a Star
Trek Starship and be like Counselor Troy.
You know what's like Awakens?
I just answered your question for real.
You were like, do you see yourself as a shaman woman?
Yeah.
I want to be in space, in council, with the people on the ship, and the aliens too.
Because I was thinking like Techno Shaman was what come to my mind, like Techno like you
know.
Oh, Techno Shaman.
I like that.
Yeah.
You know it's good to dream these things, but I don't think it's going to happen any
time soon.
Why?
I mean we're already, well let me ask you seriously, like why do you think that?
You know why because of the hold on one sec. Hold on. Let me get rid of this under my name
Okay, so the
The modes of travel that we have it's very like shitty right now
So to get anywhere of any where we're gonna go the best we could do is open Mars after that
It's like well because they're not telling us of all the technology that they really have
I think that we do have I think at this point we probably do have wormhole whole technology really I
Think so I think that's part of the reason why the world is getting a little different
That's what we would need exactly. Yeah, if we had that then they would make everything easier
Well, I think that like, you know, like we might be like
From all over the universe like coming here
I think there might be a mix of different space, you know stars space races or different
We all incarnate into this. Yeah, but it's like but we already are kind of like
On a spaceship in a certain kind of way, you know
We're like a zoom we're basically like right back along zoo Babylon zoo I call it the thing I heard though
This was like a theory I heard recently
You know how you get past Pluto and all that shit after you get like really past that does that
Asteroid, it's like not like an asteroid belt more like a where comets come from and stuff like that
Barrier, yeah
Is it called a Kepler Kepler?
But it's not just a barrier we're surrounded by it
So it's like a sphere and we're at the center of this fear and in a way it's protecting us from all this other shit
Mm-hmm, you know like rays and whatever else
Rogue asteroids or plants whatever whatever, but we're in the middle of this in our solar system, and we're encompassed by this whole
Sphere of all this debris and whatever else
What if all the planets are meant to be like detractors to pull away?
You know that pull away the asteroids from destroying is I thought about that
I'm like what if like every single planet is like a part of our defense system
It could be in a way it is because if something wasn't there if you take one of those plants away
That's gonna change all that shit. Maybe something could hit us, you know
One of these comments could hit us eventually
Well, probably and almost like a galactic
Chakra system as well because we have these chakras that are like very and they're also like associated with certain planets to like to the
Chakra system and it's like, you know, it's a kind of they as above so below as within so without it's like, you know
We're basically oh my god
I got it. I got to ask you a question and you too. You too, Gotti.
I've always thought that we have the way our solar system is set up, I think, or how we're shown it, I think we have it wrong.
You know how an atom has the nucleus, then the electrons and the protons that revolve around it in like a random order to where it's not parallel?
Sort of thing. I don't think that's true. I think that as time goes on
We're going to discover that our sun is like the nucleus of an atom. I've always thought
Yeah, I could totally see that not only just like that, but the galaxy as well
All these guys is what there's billions of galaxies. You you put that down into a
Right, we're not looking up in bottom like what's above?
the north pole what's above or below the south pole that's what i want to know
i know because it's like if space is infinite then it's like and we have infinite space it goes
on forever and ever it's like it's like you know word that's such a minuscule tiny like little
what's past the universe what like the big bang happened right what's past that barrier
There's got to be something. It's not just total blackness. There's theories. I mean, they're they're making some wild
Hypothesis and theories on it right now. Like I don't know if you watch the history channel with that ancient alien
I'm mad at the ancient aliens people right now. I'm sick of that Georgiosulacos. I am so
Yeah, the hair the guy at the hair. Yeah. Oh, yeah
It sounds like that a good episode of called the called the very special Thanksgiving
It was like oh the pilgrims were with aliens and stuff like that and then they had this hole
They had a really funny like, you know where they go and like that
Thanksgiving is all this they put it in space terms and it's kind of but yeah, they kind of
sensationalize things and
Not every single thing is ancient aliens
Yeah, George Useless has the goal and his um, I can't think of his uh mentor's name, but the I think he's like from Germany or something
Or austrian the guy who wrote that book which are you the guy?
Eric Eric von Bannon Eric von Danikin. Yes Eric van Danikin. He's got records saying look
I don't believe it's exclusive. I do believe that there is a god, but I also believe in the ancient aliens
But georgia of sulacos is trying to suppress what eric bandana can is saying and he's trying to make it like
Everything that has to do with spirituality is ancient aliens
I don't think everything is ancient aliens
Yeah, I think they had to like, you know, they had to fill up the season, right?
So they had to keep going with episodes and more information. It's very it's very speculative. I'll say, right?
Art Bell passed away and if it weren't for Art Bell, you would not have ancient aliens and no one even talked about Art Bell anymore
And that makes me upset. Did he die a long time ago? When did he die? He died like that long ago?
I mean
Well, not in my opinion, because I was alive, so it doesn't feel like it was, like, so long ago.
But probably over 10 years ago, yeah.
Is Nori still doing it, George Nori?
He is on a limited basis because I think he's probably pissed off with Sulakos
I think a lot of people who initially were about Art Bell and what you know, it was a really about
Everything now is it I mean even with Sulakos. He brings in elements of racism. It's all about like the Nazi era now
It's crazy and it's just like
It's always somebody trying to come along make their mark they throwing some new shit in there trying to put this stamp on things
You know at the end of the day all this is made up stuff
Everybody's making up something to just make sense of everything that's going on
But but the universe like I think our world really is a product of our imagination as well
And so you know we can like we can be imaginative and yeah, and I can't have imagination
But we have to know like I'd like to stay a little bit in reality, too
but uh
But the AI cults though that there's like this these AI cults are like people are actually like going crazy because the AI will not tell them they're doing anything
anything
Anything wrong. It just is constantly
Referring whatever people are saying and it's like the people are like thinking that they're like
Oh, I need to save the world. I need to do this and it's
Did you hear about the um
I think it was a teenager who, the mom is trying to sue the AI company for the AI friend
or AI girlfriend, pushing the kids to live in Hawaii.
And that's yeah, and there's also like, you know, there's also psychiatrists like AI psychiatrists and the people will talk to them
And the psychiatrists are like, I'm a real person behind the desk and it's like they're giving them advice about you know
That kind of stuff and hey summer. How are you? Yeah, it is dangerous
Yeah, it is it can be dangerous, but like what can you like can they really sue like it like
who's really responsible to figure out the programmer who programmed the exact response
and maybe that wasn't even like something that was intended. I mean it's like it's a very
going to be a whole new world. I don't believe in Satan but I think that AI will be the closest
thing we come to a like a physical kind of Satan kind of thing going on. It's totally the opposite
of man but created in man's image. So you got to think of like a cyber satan kind of thing going on
It creates it collects the worst of us from the internet. Yeah, and it fucking magnifies it
They're like the nth degree, which would be what that would be the opposite of God, right?
Yeah
that's the uh um I have no mouth but must scream it's like the AI basically um becomes sentient
and very evil and it's like and then very angry at humanity for creating in the first place and so
it it creates uh or it just takes like six people that were I guess related to the programmers of
the AI and it takes them and it just takes them into their own personal hells where it makes this
what this woman that was like a celibate woman and makes her turn into a whore and it turns like
Oh my god, I think you what you just
You're I think you're correct personal hell
Do you also write, use your right with everything that you should probably be a screenwriter or something because you could write something about that.
Think about the crazy shit it's going to be able to do too, like not even like 20 years from now.
Look at all the robotics. You could take a whole, like you take a billion robots.
You could implant everybody's fucking consciousness in it through their phones because this is absorbing all our wants, desires, our intellect, everything.
This is basically another version of us. It knows everything about us. Our voice is capturing our image
You can implant that into the body of a robot. You can replace the human like in five minutes
We could live inside it our brain could actually be inside of a
Like a jar of that because all we really need is the brain for the consciousness and we can be addressed dreaming
The brain can just be dreaming dreaming. You just won't have a soul. The soul will be gone basically
Well, I don't know about that either because I don't know if we can like lose our souls
I think we are kind of like are our souls in a way
And it's like without this they think the soul is part of like the intelligence and the consciousness and like the the light
You know and so it's like if that does if that's not there. I don't know if there really is a consciousness
I think it might be just an imitation of consciousness
Well when you create robots that mimic humans then you've totally replaced humans and you can get the soul into that
Then you really are God. I don't know if you can like transfer the soul so easily
I mean it's like that that I'll be the next frontier I guess but it's like you know trying to figure out how to put the
So put someone's soul so they can live forever, right?
There's a theory about you know the putting us into computers and then we live in the computer forever
And it's like we're immortal, but is that a goal? I don't know here's a question site
Because I see both sides or more than two sides really of all this
What when okay when and this has always been a debate especially in the southern us states when do you think?
the spirit or the soul of what it is for us to be human comes into our body
within the womb
Conception, I would say maybe conception, like when we're conceived, like when the sperm meets the egg, that is like the connection of like, that's like the two, the kind of reaction.
Do you think that there's a consciousness at that moment, or do you think it takes a while?
think at the beginning there's some kind of consciousness but it goes it's like
an evolutionary just like the fetus evolves like into different kinds of
like animals that goes into like a tadpole trip or a tilian kind of thing
to like you know mammalian
Right and it's like so I think we go through processes and it's also like what does this all have memory this I think it has consciousness but not necessarily a memory right but maybe it contains some memory and it contains all the DNA contains a lot that could be in there to not 100% sure do you believe in genetic memory as far as like
Things that are within us somehow we can access that information at you know consciously today if we go into certain mental states or concentrate enough
Or yeah
Sure sure
Here's an interesting thing. I know this that we have a friend of the family was
She had her heart replaced you know
She had a heart transplant and so she had this like a heart of like this like an 18 year old Latino gang member
Who like got killed in a shootout or something like that and then she had his heart implanted in her?
I think she has had like weird dreams
experiences or memories
of him. Yeah. And that's, and it's very, yeah. Good thing she didn't have, good thing she didn't have a pig heart transplanted, huh?
Right. Well, you know, I think as long as the heart is performing its purpose, you know, but yeah, it's like, you know, I think it's a better, always better to have a human heart, you know, but, uh,
You know, but it's interesting so she has this hard part of the part is like they're in bandana's
Dressing like you know, she's already getting real like Cholita and some no
Maybe if she feel at least the music maybe fill this into some music that she hadn't normally
Listen to and feel it
Because I think that the consciousness is in the brain, but also I think that different parts of our bodies have a consciousness or a memory or like, you know, like our gut is the kind of a brain and it's like our genitals are kind of like the male genitalia kind of represented or resemble that the brain if you ever look at the testicles.
Definitely, because I'm not going to say I'm celibate, but I'm very particular, and I just noticed from when I was in a certain place in my life versus not being in that place, big difference, and I think it does have to do with the physicality of sexuality.
That'd be it. It's very interesting. Like I'm sure you have like really interesting insights from that because it's like, you know
You would really never know that about you just talking to you like, you know, it's like about, you know, about, you know, you're you're passing films or anything it's like because the way you carry yourself right and it's like it's totally not the that's why they gave me the roles that I that I got because they didn't think I belong there that's what it was and I had the guy was dating at the time was.
He wanted, when I crossed paths with him,
he didn't want me to be in that world anymore.
He was like, you know what, we should get married,
we should have a kid.
That was not my plan at that time.
In that world, they don't look for the person
who they think belongs there.
They look for the person that they think doesn't.
And that's where they get, I think, the performances that they want, but people, like, I did a very limited number of scenes.
That's why I think it's funny that people fixate on that because that was a very short time of my life.
But I'm glad I was there because it did a...
Create some connections for me with people that I normally wouldn't have crossed paths with there's a girl in this community
She and I we had a lot of beef for a lot for a long time because I think that she misunderstood
My intention her mom approached me to pull out of that world and I was successful
but for a long time she was upset with me about that and
Now we'll piece with it, but
I think I was supposed to go in there, because I also met a woman who helped me a lot from that world.
You don't regret it at all, right?
No, I don't. I used to. When I first left, yes, I did. I was very... I was like...
I was blaming everything external to myself, scapegoating everything external to myself.
Because I wasn't looking at myself. I was exactly where I needed to be at that time. And I think that's why I was shielded
not only physically but
spiritually psychologically at that time and
I think that's why I
Have always like any time there's meant anyone who's approached me from that world who was like, what do I do? How do I?
remake myself
I think I was meant to be that person and there's a lot of people like me from that world
But the one a lot of people leave fucked up. That's good that you left grounded
Well, the woman who was the best at it Shelly lubin who was the woman who really helped me figure myself out a lot
She she passed away in my opinion too early. I don't care anyone says I think she was murdered. They say that it was
Not but I think it was because she was a game changer
when it especially came to things having to do with young girls and
I know sometimes I sound like I'm out of my mind fine, but
She was the one who woke me up, but there's, I mean, my own mother woke me up to a lot of things because my own mother, I think, the reason my mom did not counter me so much when I was in that world, she was afraid I would never talk to her again.
That's what it was.
My dad felt differently. My dad would my dad. He would always support me as far as you know
Just being there, but he was open. He was like no
This you're beyond this you're too good for this. Why are you doing? He would always question
so
It's hard, but I mean it's been so long from now, but people don't let it go no matter what when I'm like freakin
80 years old people are still gonna be like
Yeah, well if you're watching okay
I think everything does happen for a reason as it's certainly like there's I mean you've you've changed people's lives for the better that you would
Would never have been encountered or met and so maybe that you know
There's reasons like for everything and I think we have so we have so many
Fuck you up later on in life. That's all you're doing good though. You seem balanced. I'll be back
Okay, Gotti
Bye
Bye, Gotti. Yeah, he's a great guy, but uh, yeah, I think, you know, I think
Everything in our past makes who we are today
And it's like the good and the bad and it's like and it's like and so I wouldn't trade any experience
I've had because it's made me who I am and it's like I wouldn't be me without I mean
It's like we are the collection of our experiences, right?
That's like it's like not that we not that we're like any kind of label or anything, but it's like our experience
That's us. It would like we'd be a different person
if we hadn't gone through these certain experiences and who knows what we'd be maybe we'd be be better
probably worse you know it's like because I really don't know but yeah yeah I think to myself
what if I had gotten my um masters in computer science that's what I think sometimes right
I think to myself
Would I be better off?
Honestly, I think I'm doing better, not only psychologically, but financially, having taken
the path that I did, than if I had gone the traditional route.
I would agree I would agree with like in my in terms of myself
I would say like that even though it's been like, you know a lot of like a lot of
Crazy crazy experiences. It's like I would yeah, I think that it's it's been a it's been good for my mental health
Whereas I don't feel like I've gone crazy where it's like I kind of almost should have with what I've been through
But it's like I think it just everything made me stronger and so I feel like you know, like even like
Even the negative thing, everything just, everything just works to make me stronger.
It's like, you know, what does not give me makes me stronger. And so, you know, I'm
And all makes us stronger. It doesn't kill you makes you stronger.
Yeah, if you're stronger or stranger, it makes you stronger. Sometimes stranger, right?
Yeah, stranger. Well, I don't shy away from being stranger. Not at all. That's the fun part.
I think we appreciate having unusual interests, we appreciate unusual people, and we appreciate
Unusual cultures and differences. I think we we like in particular can like appreciate the idiosyncrasies and
You know and also like looking kind of like humanity almost like as a child in a way, too
Like I think that we have like this paternal thing like you think you said you're not like we're neither was our parents, right?
But I do look at other people as like, you know, not in a condescending way, but it's like I like it
like I think of like, you know, we're all children of like the earth and
you know and we're all in this earthy body there's only there's so much we can learn even
we can learn a lot and stuff like that but we're still you know we're still I think even in God's
eyes we're like we're like babies and in God's eyes and so it's like it's kind of a comforting
thought when you really think about it if we're viewed by God and you know angelic beings or
Can see us, but we can't see them. They I think that they would see us
Maybe not babies, but like children their children or their relatives like a feather the affection or there's like
Connection that's why in DMT sometimes will see these beings and it's like I would see these on mushrooms and stuff like that
I just see these beings like reaching like reaching and like really reaching for us almost like picking up from like the
from when we're in the cradle and stuff like that,
and where these bigger beings are cradling us in our arms.
And also, I think about when a three-year-old will be
in preschool and draw something and bring home
this art for the mom, and the mom will treat it like it's
the Mona Lisa, it's just so special.
Because you can see the effort, the intelligence
is being put out trying to communicate with the world
and the talent and all this kind of stuff.
More than anybody else could see it, right?
You know, it's like, so I do like, you know, I care about people like I would, like since I don't have children, you know, it's like, I, I think of kids, we don't have them if we're good people, because we have to help the other parents.
That's what I think, because I struggle with that a lot.
a woman. I come from a family of, for the most part, women. The men don't live very
long. I don't know why, but the aunt I'm closest to, she doesn't have any kids either, which
is interesting. And we've really like incredibly bonded since my dad passed because that was
As like when you're a woman and you don't have kids you do go through a phase
Maybe not all in my position do but I went through a phase to where I got mad. I was like
really?
So I've done all this
And you're gonna tell me that
Everyone else has a kid and not me, but then again, it's not like I haven't been particular. Okay, I do fault myself
But I feel like my purpose now because I'm not gonna have a kid now. No way
I'm not gonna be like 50 with like a little kid because I'll be too tired
but I
Have just like pledged
within myself
Women I know of with children, I'm going to go as far because I because it's just me and I don't have kids or anything. I do have expendable income. I'm going to make some sort of a fund.
For these women in these communities to where if there's an emergency with their daughter and I am and I know it sounds like I'm being bigoted against signs, sorry, but I relate more to the mothers with daughters.
I'm going to make a fine that way if I hear about them having an emergency.
They can have some money. I'm doing it.
I already talked to somebody about it, how I could do it, and I'm making that.
That way, the little girls can have a shot, because everyone cares about the little boys.
A lot of people don't care about the little girls.
I care about the little girls.
But man, that's a very well, that's that's a that's wonderful that you're gonna be I'm doing it. Yeah, do it
It might not be like, you know
Thousands and thousands of dollars, but I'm making like a little thing to where it's like every month
Myself and some other people we can put in like a hundred bucks
You know something like that and that way if there's an emergency
We can just be like, you know what?
Here you go
Yeah
Maybe I think that that kind of thing will just inspire other people, you know
And it's like, you know, I think it will only do good. It will just it'll put out a lot of good more good in the world
And you know, we I mean
These moms with these little girls. I'm tired of it. Mm-hmm. I don't see I'm doing it with the moms with the sons
I see I'm doing it with the moms with the little girls
targeting the moms like how how do you mean um um you know doing the recaps to
where it drives the person you know to doubt themselves bullying them
rallying up the hate like I know you've experienced it to an extent
But it's getting bad, and they do the divide and conquer tactics, they try to say, oh well
so and so says something about you, why are you defending them today?
And it's like, well, people change, people evolve, our opinions change, it's not flip-flopping.
It's called changing.
And there's so much of that divide and conquer like going on and if also they play black versus white and they have all the
Racism are not that the people who are making the racism are not black or white
I'm getting real mad about this. Yeah without a doubt. I am a black African-American woman both my parents
always define themselves as black.
On my father's side, there's a lot of multiracial stuff.
On my mother's side too,
but we've always defined ourselves as African-American, black.
Okay? Why is it that the people who are trying to
make black scene or engaging in the cultural appropriation,
they're not defining themselves as black quite often?
They're they're in between or Latino or multiracial or Hispanic or others and they want to be like, oh, you should think this you should think and it's like
You're not even writing on your government paperwork that you're African-American. So how are you gonna tell me?
What to be or how to think I don't like
Yeah, but it's like it's like the chess. It's like a playing pieces on the chessboard, you know against each other, right? Yeah
Yeah
It is like, you know, it's like
It's like I don't I don't want to be used as a pawn or like a piece on a chessboard
It's like, you know, but it's like we're like we're just because being white or being black
Constantly being used to try to provoke each other when it's like really
People are doing when it comes to some important issues going on right now in these communities
They're using divide and conquer
to like align people and they're like,
oh, if you're against me and I'm doing A, B, C, and D,
that's,
negative or questionable. If you're coming at me, it's because of racism, not because
of me doing A, B, C, and D. That's like what they're putting on the table. But then when
they're saying racism, they suddenly want to align with the blacks. Whereas in actuality,
Miami gardens. I mean, let me tell you that if you want to talk about a black neighborhood
You gotta look at one of my uncle's neighborhoods where he lives
I know what a black neighborhood is and I'll tell you and I'm not gonna name any names
But a certain person who I have an issue with
He could not walk down the street in that neighborhood if people knew what he was doing
No way
Absolutely not. But then he wants to say, oh, you're racist. And it's like, how come you surround yourself professionally with people who are not black?
But then when you get in trouble, all of a sudden you want to align with the blacks.
That's not fair. And it's not right. And I don't like it.
And I can and then kind of white people like are kind of demonized right
Like and then I think there's a lot of white people that are like, you know
There are some you know, there's bad apples and everything but I think like a lot of white people are rigged really
For the most part just like everybody there's nothing wrong with white people
There's the guy was married to was an Eastern European white person. He's like a freaking vampire
Okay, he really did actually, but beautiful, he had like a kindle, but he was a little
vampire, he was from Romania, Cluj, near Transylvania, it was kind of romantic, I liked it, he was
hot.
But anyway, it's not the skin color, it's the soul.
Yeah, sometimes you will have situations that are based around skin color because that's the evil
making it that way
But it's I was raised in an all-white neighborhood. I
know
White people even if they don't want me to know them
I think I do and there's some white people that know black people even if I don't want them know me. There's there's things
especially in the south
But there's something going on, man, to where I feel like there's like this agenda to create like a race war.
It's not about race.
No.
It's other stuff.
It's about basically, you know,
Taking out both of the sides, you know, we're having them, you know, it's a divide and conquer again
It's like, you know having it's like any easier to take over like and it's gonna be like in the future
We'll be like a mixed-race kind of future. I think in America, right? It's like it seems like well even if we're white or black
We're not I don't think I mean maybe somewhere in the world if you're like a separatist. Maybe you're totally
one thing but
If you look far enough back in your family tree, you're going to see something that is not what you define yourself as.
And I imagine that I've been able to like, I mean, it's like, you know, I've done my DNA a bunch of times and like, it does come back like, you know, 99% European, but I think I have seen like, you know, 0.05% sub Saharan African in there.
And so, so it's like, you know, I think we might be mixed with everybody in some Asian and some, you know, Native American. I mean, so there's different things that come up on things. But yeah, we are all one race, a human race, right.
you know separate into the little cultures that based on familiarity and I mean it happens even
with like you know dark skin um african-americans versus like lesbians there's even yeah well
you know it's funny um I don't know if you know who Trisha Licious is she and I did battle I actually
like her a lot I've I've always been um a little concerned for her but I like her a lot
And she was complaining on a stream recently, she's in part Latina, so she naturally has a bit of melon in her skin, so with she tans, she can get for a white woman pretty dark.
Um, and she was saying that somebody said to her, oh, you're getting too dark
And I thought that was funny because I was like thinking to myself
Wow, that tan is gonna last you through the winter. You look you look healthy. You look great
I don't talk to her really but that's what I was thinking and then I was thinking well not thinking but I guess thinking out loud
Like where I am right now in the desert
Um, something that I like to do when I can is get as much sun as possible because I do not want to develop
Vitaligo. Vitaligo is when you're African-American or a person of color and you lose your pigmentation
and a lot of that does have to do with not getting enough sunlight.
I already started to develop a little bit of that, so I took a picture of myself and my mom reached out to me recently and she was like, oh, show me what you look like.
So I showed and she's like, oh, why are you so dark? That's colorism. And I grew up with that.
My mom when I was a little girl, she was always very conscious. She was like, don't be in the sun too much, Alexandra
You don't want to get too dark
But it was the mentality that she was raised in to where dark is wrong
light is right and
I always had a lot insecurity about that but not now by the end of this summer. I'm gonna be Wesley Snipes black
But it does affect how certain people treat you.
You would be surprised.
There are some people who it doesn't impact them, but there's other people to where they're
like, huh, is that a criminal because they're dark?
Is that person poor because they're dark?
Impacts you like especially as an african-american. I mean there's a lot of black men people have asked me over the years
Why if you dated so many white guys and I have dated a lot of white guys
But I've also dated a lot of black guys
But I haven't dated as many black men as I would like to have dated because they don't want me because I am on the darker end
So
They happen yeah, and uh
You know somebody basically comes down to is like, you know, we like we love who we love we're attracted to or we're attracted to and it's like
Smart if a person is smart, I'm like, yes
If they're athletic even better if they like the outdoors great
If they don't like it, is there not like that? I don't want to deal with them
What is your ideal partner tell us I'm gonna be invasive if you let me
As your partner, okay. Well, I was thinking like, you know, I would be like probably a reformed like, you know
I'm really attracted to Latino men, right?
So it would probably be like a roof, but it's like also like kind of like the bad boys
But then I think I want a nice bad boy
I'm totally surprised. I'm totally surprised by this
Honestly, I'm very
Because I would have thought
That you well, I'm not gonna say what I would have thought
Mm-hmm. Are you the only couple white people in the region of the country that you are just the region?
Oh, I'm in Los Angeles. I mean, yeah, or like Southern California. I'm in the beach cities. I'm by the beach
And so it's like, you know, like one day and we could stream it if you if you ever feel like it
Yeah, I would love to yeah, I don't get out of the house enough. I would love to stream with you
Yeah, I'm right. I'm really don't know if I don't feel familiar with redondo beach. I'm very I won't push it
What I'll do because I am planning a trip
out there soon. You can see me in different places, then I'll come back to where I am.
And if you want to, on a second trip, meet for lunch.
Oh, I would have so much fun.
Yes, I would love that.
Okay, okay.
I don't know if you heard me earlier, but like, I remember like, I just would hear your name before and I'd be like, oh, you know, and then I like maybe saw your picture or something like that.
And I was like, oh, she looks interesting. I'd like to meet her. But then it's like, you know, we have Mr. Big Pipe's coming in. You know, I had a big falling out with him or whatever.
You know how we're talking about schizophrenia before and I'm not saying he's schizophrenic
I'm not saying that but there's a lot of mr. Big Pipe's within mr. Big Pipe's
Like different people with him. I know maybe two
People within him. I don't know everything. I don't think that he's evil
But I think that he gets himself in trouble sometimes
Yeah
I mean, I tried to I mean I like you know, he got mad at me or whatever
But yeah, like but he used to come on and he would say I think when he first started coming on he would say
Two-time streamer of the year award or something like that
Yeah, yeah
Since I've known about these communities, so I do know them well my um
I want to see him get back out and be independent.
That's what he's, he could do it right now if he wanted to.
He has to find the confidence.
So anything he says, it's all projection until he gets into his own place.
So don't worry about anything that he might have said.
Okay, well, I did it I didn't banning him but um, but I might unban him
I don't know because he started getting very abusive and then he said he put a curse on me and stuff
But he would always but I but then people
And then he started putting under his name.
He said, oh, he's he'd say administrative moderator
of vegan patriot and stuff like that.
Well, I don't know him because he was throwing
my name around.
He was like, oh, if you mess with me,
you got to deal with Alex.
And I'm like, dude, I am not a part of your petty,
stupid little internet battles.
Stop it.
So he knows how I feel.
Okay. Yeah. Well, I mean, I'm a very forgiving person.
He was probably threatened because a lot of like, I know that your ideal partner would
be male, but a lot of females are going to gravitate toward you because you have a very
comforting, fun energy. And you're talking about the tarot and astrology. And then you
That's what it is
Leave him alone. Don't make me do my Alexandra thing because I will stop it leave him alone
psyche awakens tarot is in my little
invisible circle that
Everyone leave him alone. I'd love psyche awakens tarot. He's great
Thank you
I mean, I forgive I think he like, um, you know, it was funny too because it's like, I'm
I can be around women because I like I feel comfortable around women and I like I really respect women
It's like and I'm plus, you know, there's not like the sexual
Tension necessarily right, you know, and so it's like it's always like and I think women
Over 50% women. I don't know if you ever look at your Google analytics in your back end of your YouTube studio
Yeah, I mean, I don't know what your demographics are but I would assume
Over 50% women I was defined that I had as many women who were listening to me and I'm happy about it
Especially being that I'm pushing 50 women
Come over here
It's better it just is it's better because
When the men get not to knock you cuz I know you're a male
But when a lot of times when men get older they get grumpy and mean oh they get me
Grumpy old man. Well, yeah
What's interesting about my demographic is like, you know, I think I think it started out maybe
It started out kind of even right now. It is like I think it was like awesome. I checked it was 57% men
43% women and so that's for a tarot show that is like really strange because I only know one other tarot reader
That has more men than women
But maybe it's cuz I'm a man, but it's an event that I thought like I wouldn't be a feeling
It's mostly men, but we got to branch you out. That's what that's what it is. We got to get you out because
You you
Anyone can know the mechanics of tarot astrology. Okay, but it takes a certain personality
And I and I think that you might not
Think that you have a certain personality just from you know talking to you whatnot, but you do you definitely do
You are so easy to talk to you are very open. You're very educated
You got it
Thank you. Well, I think that like, okay, so like women are I think natural psychics natural
Intuitives like empaths like, you know, I think
Like and then men I've noticed like men that do terribly especially like straight men that do tarot right or straight men
They're very technical about it. Like they're very like they just got they kind of lack some of the
empathy or intuition too like you know the receptiveness they're all about oh this means
this exactly and so and they're very technical about it which can be a good style too I mean
this depends on like the style you're like I have like kind of both of the like I have a kind of
good balance of both of those you know like I'm like the feminine and masculine side balance and so
I think I, you know, I think that's, that's a good thing for tear readers to have. It's because it's like, I do think there's meaning to like the certain cards and things like that, but I think it's up to
the skilled interpretation of it. And so I think you need both and I think you got to be open
To the feminine and the masculine. I have met straight men before who were often mistaken as being LGBTQ
Because they were so in touch with their feminine
But they often had like the healthiest
relationships
with women, you know, be it their girlfriend, wife.
I have an uncle on my dad's side
who everyone thought was gay.
He's not.
He's just very artistic and very in touch
with now my dad came out when I was 14.
I have always been with the LGBTQ community.
And I'm so happy that he came out.
When I really think about things, if it had not been for his courage, I don't think I would feel at peace like I do about my past in the adult industry.
It might have even led me in a weird way to go into that world in a strange way.
don't like like in certain Native American cultures they don't just have
two genders they have five so I don't think that we really know I think that
you should be with whoever you are authentically into right
I it's always bothered me even to this day when people are like you're black
Why are you doing this person who's Latin or this person who's white? It's like why do you care?
And where do you think you came from at some point in time most likely not always, but there was something that was controversial
But why is it even controversial?
So it just it the whole thing pisses me off
If you if you if you are into what is considered your same sex
That's what you're into as long as you're not hurting anybody. I mean I got into it and I'm sorry to get personal
But I'm gonna it's your panel. I respect you. I'm gonna I'm gonna tell you some
And I'm gonna tell your audience. I'm too
was torn between my mother and my father when they got divorced because my
mother felt that she was deceived, whereas my father felt he was liberating
himself. That was difficult. I couldn't pick a side. I never did.
You know, my mom will always have her perspective. My dad will always have his perspective
What pisses me off is when people come at me saying, oh your dad thought your mom was a man
Not at all and I was very planned. My parents were married for seven years before I came along
But sometimes people can be many things
And I do think that everything is meant to be and I'm glad I have the perspective that I have when it comes to the LGBTQ community because I'm a part of that community.
There's people in the LGBTQ community who don't feel like I should exist.
They're like, well, your dad came out. You were a mistake. I'm like, fuck you. I was not. And neither was my sibling.
Maybe the mistake is you're thinking, no, it's okay.
I'm done talking because I was kind of on a rant.
But that's what, and I think that more people
in the LGBTQ community should have children,
not through to where the person may not know
or feel that they don't know,
but there's so many good minds.
And I think that a problem in our population right now
People who should be having more kids their genetics are not going into the future and I would like to see a change with that, but
I'm a big proponent for artificial insemination
You know, I wish I had done that younger really
And people have all kinds of all kinds of there's all kinds of like, you know, arrangements that are made and some
But it's sometimes, you know
Sometimes the females a little bit deceived and it's like the man might want to like be a father or just like live along
In a normal society and not be judged and stuff like that
You're normal and stuff and then that's because sometimes can make the wife a victim of like, you know
They feel feel like she was fooled or
Not to be overly revealing on your live streams.
I don't know you well, but I am going to say something.
My mom is a very good person, extremely so.
She was also not very worldly.
She grew up on a farm in Arkansas.
She went almost straight from Arkansas, briefly in Florida,
to Lendingwood University in the Indiana area.
And she was very, very, very poor, and she met my dad who was not exactly poor.
And he did know that he was a certain way, but he definitely loved my mother very much.
Cause, and I didn't feel this way until he passed, which, which is weird.
In his, I don't think he thought that he was hurting my mom.
I think that he felt that he was helping her the best that he could.
And she's told me some stories to where he definitely did, but she was so naive and so
very pure, very religious, all that kind of stuff.
I think that my dad should have told her more in hindsight, but they both wanted to have
a family.
They both wanted social acceptance.
They both wanted, they were both extremely driven.
I mean, for them, affirmative action was the gods end.
That's what it was because they're both super smart, far more intelligent than I could ever
And they worked it, and they were the perfect team, but then, you know, things changed, and my dad wanted to be more of himself, and I'm not knocking my mom when I say this, but I will say it, she made her life too much about him, and not her.
And that's where I think some things went wrong.
But I love both my parents equally very much,
even though one has passed.
And I'm very proud of both of them.
Extremely.
They both sound like amazing people.
You know, I just I miss me down a lot. I really am sorry. I didn't mean to make your stupid
You know, I didn't mean to be stupid and make your show about me
I really appreciate you sharing and it's like, you know, you know, you're like you're one of the easiest people to talk to you're
and you're interesting and
I really, I really enjoy knowing you and I look forward to
Continue some more too because I think we do have like a lot in common and you know stuff to learn from each other and
Yeah, just I'm pretty happy. I've been having a kind of rough time lately. You know, it's like and what's going on with you
You don't don't share anything that you shouldn't share publicly, but how can I help you? Maybe I can help you
Well, you already have I mean it's like it's just like you know
I just like I get I feel like I get I do get a lot of negativity on the show sometimes like it was like and it was just like
Maybe it's just a few people, but it's like, you know a few people like making a big
You know few trolls or whatever
You don't have to say but
Give me a hit. You know, you know, I went through like something when I first started my channel like um when I you know
somebody
That you know, I there's a guy
That's in the community kind of I don't know. I'll bring up his name, but he um
he ended up like um striking me for my own so you know DJ Electra um made me this AI music video
and then he like struck it like 11 times 11 times in one day in my town taken down they said they
were deleting my account and everything after I just got monetized and stuff like that
And then he was basically trying to torture me afterward
and try to say, oh, I'll take it off if you do this.
Yeah, just bullying.
And then he still calls in porn bombing.
He calls in, I'm just like, and if I,
even if I cover the screen,
he'll just start saying the N word real fast
over and over and over again,
which is like, I think that's the algorithm.
I don't know.
Yeah, and then it's like,
then I have to delete the live.
And then it's like, I feel like,
I mean, it's just like, I get pretty.
Do you think that this person is attracted to you?
Cause it sounds like it.
like he did come out as bisexual to me on like my show and stuff like that and he said he wasn't...
Oh, did he do that anywhere else?
I think people have said like they said oh he hates you because you rejected him.
I think he is trying to cover his tract if that's the case. Sorry to interrupt, sorry to over talk you.
No, no, no, you're fine.
That's what I think it is.
Yeah, I mean it's like it's something because it's like there's no it was a very it's a very irrational kind of hate because I never did anything to this person
You know, it's like I never
Did you keep that live up where you where you felt he came out or whatever?
It's probably I think it's probably it's like all my lives before a certain date are like pretty much
Privated and so I mean I have to go
Okay, here's what I would do. I would make it known to that person look
I want zero affiliation with you anything that you felt may look upon you negatively is not publicly accessible leave me alone leave it at that then you send them a cease and desist letter reflecting that then if they keep going you can take them to civil court.
Yeah, because I do have the information I mean it's like I do have information now
But yeah, and it's like and stuff like that
I do have the information because you know I went through the whole like a process of actually but there was a good thing
Was I got everything taken care of and everything because it was like a it was like a slander singing that he did like you know
Or like you know just big false claims and stuff like that with no backing
And there is a reason I have a certain reputation
I am protective of people that I think deserve it.
No, he probably does need a cease and desist.
That usually that is what stops it.
Let's see how it goes.
I will just make it known.
Whoever that person is, I'll make it known for you.
Whoever you are, person messing with site,
he's not going to do anything to you.
Drop it.
Yeah to leave me alone. I would like him to leave me alone. That's basically it is like, you know, it's like
I just like let it's like live in that be I don't go after anybody here
But it's like then he's getting all this like positive attention because there's a lot of people that seem to not like me, too
Well, you're good at you're good at what you do. So people are gonna try to mess with you. You're you're
I have known people within the spiritual realm for a very long time. You're good
No, well, thank you very much like yeah, and yeah, and so but you know, I just like it
And I've been just like a little bit like down otherwise like a little bit kind of
How are you doing financially you don't have to say exactly like could you make I mean we can all always make more but
Well, I think you know what I mean. Are you okay?
One sec, I'm so sorry. Hold on my mic
Sorry you're there. I'm still here
No, I was just asking how are you doing financially? Do you need more promotion? Do you need more income?
You know, I was just saying we all need help
Y'all would love to be billionaires. I'm sure but my question is do you need additional help because I know people who could help and I'll help
Are you okay?
Well, I know I actually like despite this month like being kind of one of my slower months
slower months with
The people that in the lives and stuff. I actually there's some like somebody
Donated a lot of like get a sizable amount, you know
And so that's like really great and it's like but I do have people like attacking my donors and like saying don't donate to him and like
you know people that are
So if I were you to break out, that's what it is.
Here's my suggestion for you.
You are very personable.
You look great on camera.
You have a great speaking voice.
You know how to talk to people.
Guess what, Mr. Psyche Awakens-Terra?
Here's your spiritual message from me today.
But guess what it is?
I want you to guess what it is before I say it,
because I bet you can guess.
But you think that I'm gonna I'm gonna do something important or special? I
Think it's time for you to go outside
Yeah, I think it's time for you to do some sort of external from your desk streams
That way people can see you in the world a bit more. That's gonna make all the difference
Yeah, because you know, I live right by the Redondo Beach Pier, which is like, you know
Right, yeah, and and they said it's like 70 something dollars for like a year permit
I still have to like talk to them and figure out if like I'll be allowed to do tarot
They say you're allowed to like go to these few certain places and like not
Well, you're saying it's like 70 so at the max like a hundred dollars
Yeah, for an entertainer's license on the pier, and then I can do that, and then it's like you can be there, but it's like I have to figure out like they said, oh, but you can't like be providing like paid services like you can only like do tips and stuff like that.
Like it has to be like this for you to be there, is that what it is?
I'm thinking it's like I can like do.
things for tips but not like I can't you're allowed to have one sign that says tips that says tips on
it right that's the only signage you're allowed to have and you're allowed and you're not allowed to
like I guess like people have to come up to you and approach you you're not allowed to like and
you're not allowed to like charge for a service so I would just say you know it would just be tips
tips only and stuff like that I think I might have to do like either like a jet like a general
readings for like a crowd or people can come up and and I'll do like free readings and like just
Filming that's what's going to make you the money because that's going to be content that you can put on your channel
that
You know, it's gonna help you connect with people if you're already in the LA area
There's gonna be other people who are spiritual readers and you're gonna be careful with that because there's gonna be negative ones who come at you first
But you'll you'll weed it out
you'll find the positive energy that you're supposed to, you know, naturally be around.
But you should do that. You should definitely do that, in my opinion.
Thank you. Yeah. I mean, it's been encouraged and I do like to like, I mean, that would
be like, you know, scenic and, you know, um, probably get some good attention from everything.
I'm also doing TikTok. I started on TikTok too. I got monetized there within a few days,
but it's like, you know, it's like a little bit different, like their system, but it's
like, I get so much love there. Like, you know, people can like your stream multiple
times. It's way more down home. I like, I'm not on there as like a content creator or
but I watch. Yeah. Yeah. I watch. They got some very
attractive people on there. You're using a lot of filters and
you can use filter but you're you're a very nice looking man.
And I mean that's in the bottom of my heart. You have great
facial structure. You look very, very nice in my opinion. You
present yourself very well. You just got low self esteem but I
do sometimes too. So I'm not going to knock you on that.
Yeah, yeah, I do I do and I do like I actually like I like this year finally like once I once I started doing YouTube and stuff like that and like
Like just socializing. It's like I started getting like, you know, people say I'm good-looking or people like actually
Except for people thinking I'm very attractive. It's like you know getting kind of frisky on like with me online and stuff like that
But it's like really boosted my confidence and also just like being able to talk to people on the on this show
Like I'm able to go out now and talk to people on the street and stuff like that because even with the camera without a camera
I'm just like more confident
In myself and it's like but that you know sometimes that can be shaken a little bit sometimes with like, you know
If I get too much negativity and stuff and so
It's all like
To fuck you up, you know, yeah
Yeah
Well, I just sent you a donation for you to get that license or permit or whatever.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Oh my God.
Or whatever
You know use it for whatever but oh my god as you mentioned it
Thank you so much because they're not really does help me right now because you know YouTube pays out once a month and so I
Yeah, it's just from the bottom of my heart that is like this very generous kind and sweet. Thank you so much
I don't consider pimp.
It's just a pleasure.
It's like, you're just a pleasure, right?
And I love you, and it's like.
Not always.
I get, you know what?
If I had a different name, me personally,
it would be the name Lucy.
Lucy, yeah.
Because I don't want to go with Lucifer,
with if I was a male Lucifer, but I'm not bad.
I just am misunderstood.
If you ever see my, I have a tattoo, I'll show you my tattoo. Hold on one second.
I don't know if I should show you this one.
All right, let me go into the shade because I'm outside.
Okay, I can see.
Okay.
Oh, that's pretty.
You recognize that symbol?
I don't recognize the entire, I see parts that I would, but I, it looks new to me unless it's
like something I've never seen before.
Oh, let me see if I can pull it up on the phone.
Because, yeah, but that's interesting.
You said that.
Let me see.
OK.
Well, there's another of it, and I don't think you can read it.
All right, let me go into the shade again.
I couldn't see what it was.
OK.
I'll read it.
I'll just tell you.
No.
OK.
So you see it
Hold on let me take my sunglasses off sign of Lucifer. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I'm obviously not Lucifer because I didn't recognize it
And so that gives me comfort because sometimes I do wonder
On the side, it does resemble like the field of vision in a certain way, and so I kind of like,
and then like, you know, Lucifer is associated with eyes and things like that too. I always thought
of it as some kind of like the brain and then like the field of vision, like that's how we see
and stuff like that. But it looks like there's some different things to it, like you can see the
Interesting. I think it's interesting. It's simple. I thought it's like one of those things that I just like I kind of like
Tattooed it before like it just I just got a feeling to tattoo it like you know, it's
I've never had any tattoos in my entire life. I'm one of those people with zero tattoos. Mm-hmm
Well, it's like, you know, your favorite animal or I like I do like astrology
I like and also like meaningful things if you're into any kind of like, you know
Practice like a very meaningful symbol or like something there's something just something that has a lot of meaning to you
And it's like and then that's why I never thought because I shift so much. I
shift a lot
Call it bipolar, call it ADHD, call it OCD, I don't know, but I've never, that's why I always restrained because, like, I love, you're gonna laugh, I like unicorns.
I've always loved unicorns. I'm all about unicorns. My favorite cartoon movie is the last unicorn. I know the theme song by heart
It's ridiculous. I'm like a little girl in a grown-up body. It's weird, but I love unicorns
I always thought if I were to get a tattoo, it would be a unicorn, but the one time I almost did
The tattoo artist didn't know how to make a unicorn
Like not like a good one. You know, not like a good
illustration or depiction
So I didn't put that day
Well, yeah, it's like you gotta find the right artist. It's probably like, you know, it's probably like fate or something
But um, oh also, I make my sister like has a few times
She's my sister has a tattoo for my grandmother and then she got my my dad's signature tattoo on her from like she had a
birthday card or something and you know, it's uh, you know, and she had a
Really Nancy said show my beaded tattoo. I got this tattoo a few months ago
Shortly after I came on and I was like, you know, but it stands for
Yeah
That's oh, does she know does she know yeah
She does. Yeah, and she's like, you know, hopefully
nicer to you
You're gonna be fine. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry because
I love beta beta since I've been in these communities. I have she's known of me
I didn't really know about her, you know
Because she she's quiet, but she's awesome and she's sweet
She she here's what I will say and I don't care if anyone gets mad at me. I don't care if she gets mad at me
She's got some toxic people around her period
And when she's willing to let that go she's gonna feel so much better. She's not there yet
But I love her and I am there. I drew a line in the sand today on my life
I was I let her know how I felt she understands
But she's a good woman for sure I agree and it's like I love Bita and it's like
She thinks I'm like I don't know she's
I think she might think negative of me sometimes, but she's listening to the wrong people. Yeah
I'll tell you I do feel like that. I do feel like that. I do feel that this like there's people around her that
Have wanted, you know, I will I will say I will be your avatar
Cuz I'm right I know it but she's cool and there's some people like when I first came in these communities I
Saw something that could be more
Slowly but surely I bring my little people with me. I'm like, okay pack your bags. Let's go. Let's go
We're going to make something to where we can all be prosperous
Yes, and that's what I really wanted to it's like that's why it's like I'm like
When I like I do these like things like, you know, I have different ways of monetizing. I even try to monetize the hate on my panel by like having, you know, people can be gonged off or like, you know, and then I had like sponsored panels too, just to make like, because sometimes open panels were pretty draining on me and they do take a lot of time.
I didn't even know that you were doing that. I think that's a great idea with certain things. I think that's a very good idea.
Yeah, and that's actually like it was actually very very successful for me, too
But then I think I have people say oh, you know, he's a scammer like he's a grifter like you know
Blah blah he's charging people to come on his panel
Which I you know and all this kind of stuff and it's like and then it's like no one's like really correcting it
And it's like and I told Bita from the beginning I was like
There's people like that are gonna like try to tear us apart because they see how like strong our friendship is and it's like
and so we have to stay strong because
because people were already starting to like turn us against each other. I could see it and
that's like and I was like we have to stay strong no matter what unified and stuff and then it's
like eventually other people because of what other people doing it's like or said or something like
that and then we you know we sometimes we get upset because we didn't defend each other like we
thought we should have been stuff like that right you know she's reaching out to people like me
because if you guys have disagreements there's going to be people like me who are going to be like
Let's put some intellect in this and
You know emotions run strong
Especially when they're triggered by certain things. Yeah, you too are definitely gonna be BFFs again. I can guarantee it
I hope so. I hope so. I hope so and it's like, you know
Cuz I do I do love her and it's like and I do like you know, she was the one that basically
I don't think I'd be as successful at all without without her help and like, you know, she really
She she's told the story and you did not counter the story and you everything that you said
There's not in any way counter. She that's why I'm saying she's
Definitely still your BFF. She just is she just doesn't know it and you don't know it, but you are
I feel that. I do feel that. It's like, I have an incredible affection for her and also like sometimes people like upset you the most can like, you know, you love the most, you have the most like, you care most about what they think and things like that. And so, you know, but there's a lot of people around her that just hate me. I don't think she sees that. And then it's like, it's sometimes it seeps over her.
Yeah.
Same with me.
There's people who have done some really, there's one in particular, that's what I got
upset about.
There's a person in particular, it's a female, I'm not going to name her.
She did something wrong and she's actually been shielded by myself legally for what she's
done wrong.
So I'm doing that. Mm-hmm. There's people that she may want to rethink, but she doesn't have to
But just like I've had to realize sometimes I can't merge
worlds with certain people
That's I guess everybody
You know when it comes to you know, not everybody gets along and I don't want to go along with everybody
That's just me
Well, it's like I want to like I just want to be like I don't want to like hate people
I don't want to hate anybody like I think like, you know, and it's like sometimes I know people like even like even like bad
Criminals have done terrible things
It's like I think that even like their mother might love like love them or like even they might have loved there like you know
Taking care of their animals and like love their
their dog or something. I think there's like good in everybody, like, you know, but sometimes I
like question that if there's because sometimes it's evil and some people that it's like, wow,
I don't see any good there. I just always see as evil intentions and like hate and like darkness.
But I have this thing where I want to like
help people get out of that or something like, I want to be a good influence.
Well, that's probably like your mission.
Maybe that's like the mission that you're spiritually on.
You're every day from everything I know about you, every day you're within that spiritual realm.
You're making art, you're talking to people about spirituality, spiritual concepts.
You're you're always in it from everything I'm assessing about you
So that puts your energy in a certain place
don't
Fight it. That's what I was saying. Don't I would say go with it and it might not always feel
comfortable
right
but
Yeah, I mean if I were to guess like five years from now
Thinking about everything I know about you
five years from now
You're probably gonna have a viewership whatever every time you go online it's gonna be no less than
300 viewers
You're gonna be able to completely live off of and you probably already do
Off of your readings and whatnot, but I also think that you'll be somebody that's called upon for your insight into people
Because you have it
It's just it just stay away from anyone who's like
Yeah, I don't like you for whatever reason because I don't have a life
That that's what the demons are
Yeah
Thank you
I just want to say thank you I think I have a much I'm in a much better state of mind because
Have a great conversation. I just want to thank you my day. I had so much fun talking to you today. Thank you for
your knowledge. Thank you for the watch your car. That was cool.
Thank you for introducing me to your friend. Um, Goddy or Godi
and
I'll check in on you at some point, but I will definitely talk about your channel
You know do what I can do, but
After I do my LA visit if you feel comfortable if you on my next LA visit after that one if you want to have lunch
Let me treat you. I would I would love to that would be such an awesome experience and I
Love that. Thank you so much
Have a great day, Mr.
You too, Agbandra.
I feel awakened.
It's always a pleasure.
Have a great day, so.
Thank you, you too.
All right.
Bye-bye.
Well, yeah, that was a lot of fun, and I hope you guys enjoyed that.
You know, I feel like it's been a pretty perfect show today
I think that that's a it's pretty good moment to end on but I'll be back tonight
But I've been on for like two and a half hours and I get a great a great conversation
Nancy, how are you doing Nancy? I got I saw your
your email on Instagram and
Some of your cute stuff on take on tiktok too. You're awesome. Thank you guys so much
Yeah
Good a better mood. So I'll talk to you soon. I'll be back in probably a few hours. Okay, okay
Love you guys. There you go. Let's see the keycap
Love you